# **DHRUBAJIT KONWAR**

6001443974 | dhruvkonwar65@gmail.com | NEW DELHI, INDIA 110030

## **Summary**

Ambitious and motivated entry-level professional with a foundational knowledge of HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. Passionate about full-stack web development and committed to continuous learning, staying up-to-date with emerging technologies and growth. Excited to contribute to projects, learn from experienced professionals, and make a positive impact within the industry.

### **Skills**

- \* HTML
- \* CSS
- \* Javascript (JS)

- \* React Js
- \* 00PS

# **Projects**

#### **Web Portfolio**

- \* Developed a visually appealing and responsive web portfolio using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, and JavaScript. Utilized HTML5 and CSS3 to structure and style the web pages, ensuring clean and well-organized code.
- \* Implemented smooth animations and transitions using CSS3 and JavaScript, adding a polished and professional touch to the portfolio.

#### **DrumRhythm**

- \* Designed and developed a website showcasing a wide range of drum kits using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.
- \* Implemented intuitive functionality that allows users to play the drums by clicking on the drum kit images or pressing corresponding keyboard keys.

## **Education**

**Bachelor of Technology**, CSE **ITM University Gwalior**, Madhya Pradesh

06 / 2018

# **Experience**

August 2022 - March 2023..... Project Coordinator, **Ayya Waste Management** - Goa, India

- \* Collaborated with a team of volunteers to plan and execute sustainable initiatives aimed at reducing carbon footprint and promoting environmental awareness in local communities.
- \* Led projects focused on waste management, renewable energy, and Eco-friendly practices.
- \* Developed and delivered educational workshops on sustainability to schools and community groups, reaching over 500 participants.

April 2019 - April 2022......Associate Sales Consultant, **Policybazaar.com** - Gurgaon, India

- \* Identified and worked to help customers to make a better choice between policies and help them select the best policy out of it.
- \* Developed excellent communication and interpersonal skills by effectively engaging with a diverse customer base and tailoring sales approaches to meet individual needs.
- \* Leveraged CRM system to manage sales activities and track sales performance.

September 2018 - February 2019...... Associate Analyst, **Global Logic** - Gurgaon, India

- \* Performed quality assurance to assess data and validate results.
- \* Created reports detailing findings and recommendations.
- \* Collected, organized and input information into digital database.